guyswithiphones.com 2019-10-27

# Guys With iPhones

## Privacy Policy

This statement covers the site [GuysWithiPhones.com](https://guyswithiphones.com/) (GuysWithiPhones), a subsidiary of the QueerClick Network. Please read this statement carefully before proceeding to access the QueerClick Network. Your use of the QueerClick Network indicates your agreement to abide by the Terms in effect.

### Information Collection

The QueerClick Network is the sole owner of the information collected on GuysWithiPhones.com The QueerClick Network may collect information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

### Comments

In order to enhance their use of The QueerClick Network, users can choose to leave comments on particular articles of interest via our third party provider, Disqus. To leave a comment, users must submit information including a valid email address. QueerClick uses this information to screen out users who leave comments prohibited by our terms and conditions of use, and will not pass this information to any other organization.

### Email Addresses & Your Privacy

The QueerClick Network does not collect email addresses from our surfers for the purpose of tracking, demographics, email or marketing communications.

Usernames and their accompanying email addresses for the purposes of Online Comments are collected and secured by third party provider, Disqus - some of this information is captured and stored in our system back-ups.

Any information you’ve provided by commenting on the website (Username, Email Address) will not be shared with any person or business. Your privacy will be respected and we will not sell, rent, share your email addresses. We will ensure list security and prevent any abuse.

You can review Disqus’ privacy policy here:  
<https://help.disqus.com/terms-and-policies/disqus-privacy-policy>

Please [contact us](http://www.queerclick.com/contact) with any questions or concerns.

### Third Party Cookies

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, The QueerClick Network has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by The QueerClick Network only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Third Party Advertising

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by a number of third party ad services. Information about users’ visit to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not username, date of birth, or any other personal information), may be used to serve ads to users on this site.

### Log Files

The QueerClick Network uses the industry standard Google Analytics to monitor usage and behaviour on it’s websites. Like most standard Web site servers The QueerClick Network uses log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, The QueerClick Network may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

### Business Transitions

In the event The QueerClick Network goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

### Links

The QueerClick Network contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, The QueerClick Network, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by The QueerClick Network.

### Notification of Changes

Whenever The QueerClick Network changes our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
